I'll
see
you
next time.
I am so not feeling today.
You should try getting
yourself into a better mood.
I mean, am I missing something because
we established that I leveled up, right?
But my numbers haven't changed at all.
Look more carefully.
Your luck has increased by three.
Seriously?
This isn't any different from real life!
Even in this world, it's like
I can never attain my dreams!
Hey, look up.
Something's starting to come into view.
It's a town!
What are you dawdling for?
Let's go, Jingle Gee!
The fluctuations in your
mood are really extreme.
It sort of has the feel of a
marketplace in Eastern Europe.
I've always liked this kind of thing.
Not like this though!
I'm gonna need you to explain why I have
to wear a bag on my
head to enter this town?
To prevent a pandemic just put up with it.
You're treating me like some
kind of zombie or disease
Making me stand out.
I really hate this world
Hello, would you be interested
in buying this for me?
I want to return to the modern age.
I want to eat ramen.
Here you go. Oh, thank you.
The guardian deity's pelt
earned us ten silver pieces.
Well, I didn't think
it would sell for much.
If it hadn't had a hole in the
chest, it would have been double.
I'll have to think about the
killing method next time.
Thanks for the snack.
Do you think you could always
just wear that thing from now on?
In your dreams?
Hey, Jinguji! What is it?
Isn't this super cool?
Ooh, let's buy it!
Who do you think would use it?
Wait, it's a weapons shop! Let's go!
If I'm gonna cut down all
the things, I need a blade!
Listen, I gave you a birthday present
once to encourage you to cook more!
And it has lain unused and unloved in the
depths of your kitchen collecting dust?
which I should mention is beyond shameful
for Damascus steel kitchen knife.
Uh-oh, this topic was a landmine.
I'm sorry about the knife!
But that aside, you need a sword
in the fantasy world, right?
I mean, come on!
You really are stubborn.
Well, I guess I did want something
other than the kitchen knife.
Yee!
This is awesome!
They're actual swords!
Do you have whetstones and knives?
What for?
Hey, now!
It's not exactly fair that
all the shopping's for you.
I suppose you're right.
If there's anything you need all you have
to do is let me know
yes if there's anything
you need let me know are you glitching i
just said i wanted this i'll be using this
knife for hunting and i'd like a whetstone
to sharpen it you
should
know
that what
you just did is exactly the type of action
i despise the most i'm
sorry as long as you
understand that was close i nearly bought
the sword unparalleled
beauty that physical
appearance is affecting the inner self as
well i must exercise
restraint so tachibana
doesn't head in a bad direction traveling
incognito hmm sorry it's obvious she's
hiding her face which just makes her stand
out more so i thought
i'd ask really Really?
That's what you think too?
I just happen to have the perfect
thing on hand if you're interested.
Enchanted hair ornament.
Turns people's eyes away. Oh?
I'll let you have it for cheap too.
How much is it?
It's just 300 gold coins.
What do you think about that?
Thank you for the knife and whetstone.
Hey, wait!
Honestly, that would be nearly all
the gold coins the villagers gave us.
You know something?
I was just thinking.
Wouldn't this be a good
time to use this face?
Like, to haggle down the price?
Well, I'm sure you could, but...
when I think that we might drive
the shopkeeper to bankruptcy...
Hey there, mister!
Do you think you could make it
just a little bit cheaper for me?
Then shall I give you my entire shop?
It worked too well.
I told you so.
Here, take the deed to my store.
Um, I really don't need it.
Is there something else you want?
Weapons?
Or perhaps money?
What must I give you for you to marry me?
I'm sorry, please forgive me!
Shopkeep, apologies.
But if you'd forget this conversation...
Shopkeeper.
What was I doing? For real?
That hair ornament earlier.
Would you still sell it to me?
Uh, gladly!
Who was that stunning beauty just now?
It was like seeing a dream
that had come to life.
I'd gladly worship a
goddess like her forever.
I ended up buying it.
It's just, it would be a problem
if we couldn't go outside.
This is sort of a last resort.
A suit?
Say, Jinguji, I've just realized
something pretty interesting.
You can make this door appear and
disappear whenever you want, can't you?
Yes.
So if I were to stay inside
and you were to travel alone,
there's no need for me
to walk too, is there?
Tati Banner,
I know you're not the kind
of person who would make
their best friend work while
you rested comfortably,
are you?
So you're saying you'd
already figured this out?
If one of us can take it easy, there's no
point in both of us exhausting ourselves,
right?
Then let's suppose that
I do travel by myself.
I'd make the door disappear
and you'd be in there all alone
Yeah, okay, if I die
while the door is gone.
What do you think happens to you?
Well,
then just leave the door out
like this can't you just think
if someone enters will you be
able to deal with them alone?
There's magic in this world.
Do you really think a lock
will make a difference?
But, when I go out, all I do is cause
problems for all kinds of people.
Therefore, this.
Well, now people aren't
even looking at me at all!
This is awesome!
Hey, don't get too excited.
It only directs eyes away.
It might be less effective
if you're worked up.
Thank you so much, Jingiji!
Now I'm free of this paper bag!
So satisfying!
But this guy stands out a
lot in his own way, too.
He's got refined features,
and he's wearing a suit.
Wouldn't it be better for
him to change his clothes?
What now?
Are you smiling because
you're so incredibly popular?
No, I'm sure you've noticed as well.
Someone's following us, and they're
emitting a tremendous bloodlust.
I totally didn't notice at all.
Why are you smiling?
You were so scary.
They're surprisingly bad at
concealing their presence.
You mean you can't feel
that aura of bloodlust?
Normal people can't sense that.
Who do you think you are, anyway?
What even are you?
Hey, I know for a fact you're
following us, so just show yourselves.
Blast you!
Showing off your flirty face right
in the middle of town for all to see!
Do you have any idea how tough we had it
after what you put us
through the other day,
you sneaky wench? Who's that?
You know, that group of
bandits from the village.
Look, don't get me wrong, I was
pretty sure you wouldn't remember us.
But I figured if we waited at the nearest
town, we'd run into you eventually.
After the fire was set,
everyone got out all right.
But the flames moved so fast,
we ended up scattered all over.
So don't mention my hair,
I'm embarrassed enough!
Honestly, your hair was not
what I was thinking about.
Let's do this big bro
yeah you're as beautiful
as ever i may just fall
in love big bro that's
something only a guy who's
already in love would
say don't look at her
shield your eyes is this a
sketch so once they're
aware of you they can be
charmed kill the one with
the glasses and then we
can sell the woman to the
nobles die for the sake
of her happiness i'm
experiencing some deja vu
Please to meet you, Mr. Soot.
I suppose it's safe to assume
that you are also a hero then.
Uh, a hero.
Since you appear to know what a Soot is,
does that mean you've come here
from the same world as we have?
Perhaps.
May I ask your name?
It's my pleasure to tell you that I am
Schwarz von Lichtenstein Lohengramm.
I will become a great hero in this world.
I'm sorry, but your name is
so long I kind of spaced.
Could you say it one more time?
Huh?
Still my pleasure to tell you I am
Schwarz von Liechtenstein Lohengrang!
It is my honor to have been
summoned to this world as a hero.
Why do you put on and take off the cloak?
Japanese?
Yes.
Then what was your name in Japan?
I've left it behind in
that old world forever.
I am a new man, so just call me
Schwarz von Liechtenstein-Lohengrom.
I have been summoned here
to this world as a hero.
Okay, that's nice, buddy.
Wait a minute, are you kidding me?
I want all the trouble of reaching out to
you, so what's with the cold shoulder now?
Do you have other business with us?
Because we don't have any with you.
Hey, let's take a breath, Jingiji.
And don't be angry.
But I can't stand seeing him like that.
Well, if you say so.
It seems obvious that he introduced
himself with a false name.
So we must be careful not to
divulge too much information.
If it proves difficult, throw in
fake details from time to time.
It wasn't a false name so much as...
Well, never mind.
Schwarz von Lichtenstein-Lohengrom.
Do I have that right?
Yes, but please call me Schwarz.
How do you remember that?
I'm Watanabe, and her name's Audrey.
How's it going?
Audrey, tell me, are you from this world?
No, not exactly.
Let's see, how can I explain this?
Ah, I'm so sorry for staring
at your face like that!
To be able to extricate yourself
from that state on your own,
you certainly aren't the average person.
That's the standard you
want to judge him by?
Um, I have a question for you.
Huh?
Are you two, like, a couple? Or what?
What happened?
Did I ask something weird?
Oh, wait.
Yeah, she's obviously
much younger than him.
They seem more like a father
and daughter than a couple.
Um, yes, the two of us are a thing.
Huh?
Well, we are, aren't we?
A real couple, I mean?
What's this all of a sudden?
We swore our love that night, or have
you forgotten already? I don't recall.
Don't deny it, you're the one who
told me to make it fake detail!
Would you just shut up?
Who says that out loud?
I mean, no matter which way you look
at it, pretending seems natural!
Stop! No!
I don't want people thinking
I'm in a relationship with you!
Hey, now, don't say that
you're gonna hurt my feelings!
Uh...
You really feel hurt? Why
is that? Uh... Uh... Well...
I didn't mean anything weird,
if that's what you thought.
Wait, what?
It can't be.
So the man is looking after
her like a father might,
but now the daughter has developed
romantic feelings for him?
Is that the trope we're going with here?
I've seen it in light novels.
Those two must have overcome
so many obstacles together.
They've lost their homelands.
Their parents have died.
Now their lives are saved and their
frozen hearts have begun to melt.
And then...
Uh...
But in that case, I don't know why
Watanabe would deny his romantic feelings.
Could it be?
Have you left a fiancé behind
in the other world or something?
It's possible a capable
professional guy like
this there's no way he
doesn't have a girlfriend.
I have a feeling Watanabe
will disappear without
a word once their journey comes to an end.
And when she realizes that Audrey
is the one who will be hurt?
For her sake there is only one course
of action I can take kind father.
Hang on, I am not her father.
Please, I understand everything.
So now allow me to call you father-in-law.
No, you actually understand nothing.
I'm a firm believer that people
who are unrelated by blood
can still have an excellent
parent-child relationship.
I agree with you on that point, but still
confused about why you'd mention it now?
You're an excellent father.
I know what you must be thinking?
Can a man who's obviously weaker
than me still protect my daughter?
Oh, you've been charmed, haven't you?
I don't know what you mean.
I've finally found an
opponent worthy of this.
I challenge you, Watanabe!
And know this, I'm going to surpass you
easily and take Audrey for my very own!
Who's Audrey again?
You are.
Cry out my holy sword, Gram!
Gram?
Like the magic sword in Norse mythology?
I thought there were tales that it cursed
its wielder to death, but he said holy.
Look, just let the poor guy have this one.
That's the holy sword, Gram.
It makes him happy.
Are you kidding?
That sword is insanely sharp!
It's off-putting.
And if we hadn't dodged,
our heads would have been doing
that same little slidey thing.
Our opponent seems quite serious.
So you can dodge that, huh?
I'd expect no less, dear father.
He's got some nerve saying that when
he came gunning to kill the noobies!
That was close!
I've never used it before
in that cutting power!
Broken out into a cold sweat, I
almost cut Audrey right in half!
I never imagined it was
something of this caliber.
At this rate, I'll destroy my whole town!
Is there any way I can avoid a fight
and still convince father to trust me?
I can't hold myself back.
It's been so long since
I've felt this excited.
My dark powers dominate.
So, I suppose it's time now...
to get serious.
I'll make them think I've got
more than this and threaten them!
This is all I've got!
Please buy into it!
I'm begging you, just buy it!
You mean that wasn't you being serious?
There it is! Thank you,
Audrey! I love you!
That wasn't serious at all.
It's all right.
Come, why not show me
what Sirius looks like?
There's no going back now!
I have to do it!
Here I come!
Prepare yourself, father!
This is my single Sirius blow! Receive it!
Oh, please don't give me that, receive it.
I've apprehended the suspect.
Oh, arrest the two that are
stuck in the ground as well.
Wait, who are you? What is this?
We are the neighborhood watch for
this town in the Merix territory.
I'm arresting you under suspicion
of the destruction of buildings
Thanks for your cooperation not at all.
I only did what was right
Well, then what else you two
will be important witnesses
Would you accompany me
to our command post?
Willingly?
We'll go.
I'm telling you!
I am a hero who's been summoned
here to save this world!
You have to believe me!
Listen, do you have any idea how
many of those we've had this year?
This is a false name, right?
No, it's not a false name.
It's my soul name.
So it's that part of you
that's causing these problems?
Heroes and such are nothing more
than hopeful rumors, anyway.
Rumors?
Yes.
Rumors about oracles saying things
like the lord of evil will rise again,
and that goddesses will call
forth heroes to fight back.
Lord of evil? Goddesses?
There's more like that one?
But I'm the real thing!
I promise you have to believe me!
Alright, fine then.
Can you prove that you're a hero?
Oh, right! Proof?
I actually have that! How's this?
What is that?
This is the proof which the
goddess has bestowed upon me.
Or something like that, apparently.
Indeed, it does seem to be the
seal of the goddess of night.
Huh, what do you think of that?
It should prove once and for all that
I am a hero summoned here by a goddess.
Which means that you...
committed perjury!
Crime upon crime, you poor fool.
Forging the seal of a goddess
is forbidden under the covenant.
Can you stop it?
This is the real thing!
So the goddesses all have
some kind of seal, huh?
Do you think maybe I've got one too?
It doesn't seem like
it from what I can see.
I don't remember seeing anything like that
when I took a bath either
Maybe it's in a place.
I wouldn't usually see
What about my back?
Can you see anything?
Well, come on is it there or not?
My underarms?
Oh, maybe my butt.
This sucks.
What's wrong?
Sorry, I tried to hold back a nosebleed
but it came out of my mouth instead.
Is it even possible to
hold back a nosebleed?
Quite lively in here today, my lord.
Lord, what do I owe the honor?
Well, I heard a rumor going around.
That there was someone strong enough to
cut down a building with a single strike.
Are you the person in question?
His treatment seems pretty harsh for
the amount of damage he's caused.
Come now, Lucius.
He's fine.
No one was hurt after all.
Really?
No one was hurt?
What a relief.
Lack of casualties aside, there is
no defense on the matter of the seal.
Trying to pass himself off as
a priest, in short, is perjury.
Huh. I see.
But in the case that the
seal is authentic, then...
It means that this man simply
needs to prove that he's a hero.
How would he do that?
Well, let us see.
A hero who would save the world
would naturally be very strong.
We'll have him show us
his abilities as a hero.
Does that sound good to you?
Yeah, let's do it.
You replied much too quickly.
It's odd for me to be the one to say it,
but shouldn't you listen
to the details first?
Wow.
To think I'd so quickly find an
opportunity to show my true strength.
So you're the type who
doesn't listen to others.
Jinguji, what is this? Oh.
A mission-based quest like
you get in games all the time!
So they do exist?
Yes, it seems they really exist.
The Merix territory is
a big distribution hub.
A lot of goods move through here.
So, of course, robbers often appear
along the nearby roads lying in wait.
Stop the living armor that's been
stealing our people's magical items.
That is my request of you!
I love you, I love you.
Thank you
so
much.
My name is what is he
doing trying to make his
awful name sound cool I
think he puts in the work No
matter what admirable wait
he smiled do you think
he heard you compliment
him oh for sure no Question